Hey everybody, we are joined by Milt
Hendrickson, the director of football
operations for the Green Bay Packers.
Welcome Milt. And in the third round,
you guys move up just a bit
>> to take Chris Mlen, a defensive tackle
out of Missouri, what did you like about
Chris? I think one of the biggest things
that stood out about Chris through the
whole process is that every time you
turned on SEC offenses and they're
playing against Missouri, you always saw
this guy out there. I'm like, who is
that? Like, oh, there he is. And he just
I think the second half of the year and
then through the All-Star process and
just the way he just gradually kept
stacking days and just is a was just
genuinely one of those guys that that
rose through the process. Now, he's got
some nice measurables. 6'4, 313, five
flat 40. That's all well and good, but
the thing I want to ask you about, he's
got Milt 11 in hand, right? Does he use
those hands?
>> He's almost he's almost got you, Rock.
Um, I think the the combination of
obviously his tag, what you're you're
you're alluding to, but his arm length
and hand size, when he gets his hands on
people, he's able to create separation
and then move.
>> I guess there's no doubt it's one of his
assets. Absolutely.
>> Now, could you talk some about his play
style? Do you do you see him as a run
stuffer? Do you see him as a pass
rusher? Do you see him as a penetrator,
tackle for loss guy? How do you see him?
I think uh and it's I think ultimately
part of the reason we valued him so much
and and and you know ended up moving up
to get him is that he can do a lot of
all of those things. Um you can see him
play the nose, you can see him play the
three tech, he can play he can play big
end. He's done a nice job when he's had
to hold the point, but he's also one of
those guys to your point, you know,
between his his pressure and sack
production, he's he's a guy that he gets
an edge, you know, you you better you
better account for him in the passing
game. attitude and culture fit are
important to you guys. How does he fit
in those regards?
>> Uh, I think he's going to fit really,
really well. He's comes everything that
we've gotten on him and in our
conversations with him and getting to
know him, he needs football. And at the
end of the day,
>> that's that's we're all here because we
need football. And he's he's one of
those guys that uh I'm very confident
will will hold that standard. your
impressions of Brandon Cece, the corner
you drafted in the second round. What'
you like about him?
>> He desperately wanted to be a Green Bay
Packer. Did he really?
>> Yeah, he did.
>> What was just just the conversations he
had with scouts uh through through the
whole process, but at the end of the
day, his play style is similar, you
know, we're talking about with Chris,
but just just a he's willing to tackle,
he can cover, he can put his hands on
people, and he's just again another guy
that needs football. You know, I've seen
I've had a chance to watch a little tape
on him and you said he's willing to
tackle.
>> Yeah.
>> I I think he'd prefer to tackle. I mean,
he's always sticking his nose in the
rough stuff.
>> Yeah. And, you know, and the way, you
know, we don't scout and set the board
for our, you know, for our division, but
you you better be able to strap it up
in, you know, in the NFC North. Now,